A few months ago I started getting these letters.
Who wrote you the letters?
"If I'm to be harmed,
"I need you to reach out to the other Howard."
Are we still together over here?
Are we happy?
A woman from our world was arrested... an assassin.
- They call her Baldwin. - She's here illegally,
and I need to find out who sent her.
- Not my concern. - Lambert, the ambassador...
think he might be working with these people.
Aldrich, they'll kill us all!
Waffe fallen lass!
Leave them.
You didn't give them anything, did you?
Your side is compromised.
I'm not saying it's your department,
but I'm sure as hell not saying it's not.
- We're fucked. - Not if we send this one back in my place.
We're after the same people.
They tried to take me out.
They might try the same with you.
Oh, my God.
Danke.
Gute Nacht.
I get to work every morning at 8:30.
I'm never late.
Howard.
Early, actually,
so I guess I get to work at 8:20-something.
Howard.
What are you doing in there? Packing? Are you packing?
- You said it might be a week. - You're gonna be living
in my life. You don't need...
Forget it.
Um, after work,
I, uh, I just grab a quick dinner,
and I get to the hospital between 7:00 and 7:30.
I read to her, but you know that.
Anything else?
Uh, most mornings
I-I stop for coffee down at the cafe.
Uh, Go. Uh, we play the board game Go.
On Tuesdays and Thursdays, I meet a friend.
His name is Andrei, and, uh, we play Go.
Jesus.
You know, they say it's so great
to meet yourself.
Bullshit.
Kind of like losing your virginity, you know?
Wait your whole life for it,
and then 20 seconds later, you're disappointed.
What are you doing?
In about six hours,
we need to become each other.
Even though, apparently, I can pretty much do
whatever the fuck I want, as long as it's not too exciting
or even remotely interesting.
If we really want to get to know each other,
let's play cards.
So, how'd you meet this Andrei?
Uh, we met at the hospital.
His sister was admitted the same day as Emily.
She's diabetic.
Any, uh... extracurriculars?
You mean...
Jesus, Howard. Are there any other women in your life?
I'm married.
Did-did you...
When she was still alive,
did you do that kind of thing?
So, let me get this straight.
Your only friend in this big old city is some guy
you didn't even know until six weeks ago?
Until six weeks ago, I had her.
What about, uh...
what about your routines?
Don't worry about me.
I work a desk job
and have absolutely no social life.
We've spent the last hour going over my stuff,
and you do I-I don't know what,
and your answer is, "Don't worry about it"?
Yeah. I got a guy.
His name is Raash. He'll take care of you.
You do realize we're the same person, right? Essentially.
I mean, the same flesh and blood, the same DNA.
Yeah. Believe me, I do.
Then why do you feel compelled to treat me so badly?
It's your bet.
You flopped top pair, and you're folding?
That was a good bluff.
Do me a favor, will you?
Play one hand like you actually know how to win.
Howard, play the fucking hand.
Are we finished?
No one will notice you here.
Fresh clothes.
Weapon?
You were in their custody for hours.
What did they ask you?
I'm sorry.
About what happened to your other.
She's dead.
And I gave them nothing.
I'll talk to them about next steps. Get some rest.
Howard, it's time.
Well, well, well.
You're saving the good stuff, huh?
That's not for me. Or you.
It's for when she wakes up.
Just one week.
You're doing the right thing.
They're gonna see through me.
Not if you keep your mouth shut.
You'll read to her every day.
I will.
Keep her safe.
Find these people.
Howard.
I'll take him, Cyrus, from here.
Thank you.
Do you have his paperwork?
Yeah.
All right. They don't do that, by the way.
What?
Shake hands. Berlin, on the other side, they...
You'll see. It's a germ thing.
Good to know.
Howard, if you are caught,
there's no one to protect you over there.
You understand? You're on your own.
Yeah.
I have to deny any part of this.
Okay. Thank you.
Danke.
Arms up.
Yours?
Oh, shit, I forgot.
Oh, come on, it's just a pack of bloody smokes.
Oh, for God's sake, it was just a mistake.
Come on, really?
Sir?
Purpose of visit?
Uh, the, uh, embassy pouch.
Welcome home.
I'm Raash.
Thank you.
Hey! Hey! What...
Come on, what are you...?
A little sparse.
I have a few contacts left at the embassy.
We'll put more escorts on Lambert.
If he has any connections to Baldwin, my men will find out.
Do you ever have doubts about these men?
I'm just wondering how we've always been
one step behind here.
'Cause we've been meticulous, right?
In our vetting. I mean, there's no...
There's no chance of any point of compromise here, is there?
Not unless you count Howard Silk.
You promoted him.
Well, that was the deal.
His other's gone.
- Why make deals? - Because, candidly speaking,
that man's been a lot more useful than your lot lately,
and I'd like to stay on his good side.
Was there anything else?
Ah, finally, they send help.
Thought I was gonna be in Strategy.
Yes, this is it. Strategy payroll.
You have a degree in accounting, yeah?
No.
Your desk.
They think what I do is a joke,
so now they play a joke on me.
Need to file every time card, mark it with code, send it back.
You take too long, I will find someone to replace you.
Questions?
Uh, where are you going?
Personal day.
What is wrong with you?
This is all his idea, I assume?
Groceries.
So, this is it?
Just you and me, locked in this apartment for a week?
God, I'm such an idiot.
Open the door.
I just saw Raash go in there.
I know you're in there.
Dad!
Your phone's been off all day.
Mom's in the hospital, we've got to go, come on.
- Mom? - Yes.
Your mom?
Obviously. What... get your jacket.
Come on. Come on.
Anna?
What?
What, uh... what happened to your mother?
It was another overdose.
Yeah. Neighbors found her on the floor.
Barely had a pulse.
She'd probably been there all night.
You're actually surprised?
I-I'm a lot of things right now.
Yeah, well, don't worry. You don't have to do anything.
I'll deal with the doctors when we get there.
Right.
Yeah. O-Of course.
I see you.
Two escorts now.
For some reason, they think I'm using these appointments
for clandestine meetings.
So, where is she?
She wants to keep working.
Says she told them nothing.
Told you she told them nothing.
Have you heard anything from home?
Towel, please.
Your friends are not happy
with how things have been developing.
They want to bring over our guests earlier than expected.
She hasn't removed the targets yet.
And on that note,
they also raised questions
about your assassin friend.
First they push me out of an airplane
and then they take away my chute.
They want her removed.
She trusts me.
That's putting it lightly, from what I hear.
Perhaps it's time
you actually use that situation to your advantage.
Clare.
I can't imagine the pressure you're under.
The weight of these expectations.
But after all the work that they did to place you here,
would you really risk this mission
when we're so close to the big day?
I'll take care of it.
You always do.
How are you feeling?
Thirsty.
Jesus, Em.
What happened?
There some reason you're here, Howard?
I'm...
Well, thank you for coming.
- I've got it. - Could you...
put your dicks away, please?
"Light a candle at St. Christopher's."
What the fuck does that even mean?
You want to know what I'm thinking right now, you prick?
I'm thinking this is on you.
Stay the fuck away from her.
Really? Just walk out in the middle of the day?
You want to be any more conspicuous?
That was your idea of a promotion?
- Payroll? - Well, I'm sorry.
It was the best I could do with ten seconds' notice.
Okay, what do you know about this, uh, Lambert?
Nothing.
I don't know, we got men on him all the time,
but he's a high-ranking diplomat, so...
- Really? - What?
You're married to a director's daughter, right?
Yeah. So?
What the hell's my marriage got to...?
I'll have you know i was on my own career trajectory
long before I met Roland Fancher's daughter.
- Okay. - Yeah, and I resent the implication.
I'm fucking good at my job,
and when it comes to my work, Howard Silk,
nothing gets past me.
So I guess you know all about other Howard's wife, then, huh?
She was an agent.
Housekeeping? Under Aldrich.
How do you know that?
'Cause she was my contact.
She reached out to me months ago,
said things on your floor were compromised,
she couldn't trust anybody,
and then she had a little accident.
But you know all about that, right?
'Cause nothing gets past you.
Get back to the fucking Office.
I'm meeting a friend this afternoon.
Who?
An old friend. Don't worry about it.
All right, we're gonna have to establish
a few fucking ground rules here.
Both of our lives are on the line
because of this arrangement,
so you can't wander around my world
like it's your fucking playground.
We're in lockstep from now on.
So who is this friend, and when are we meeting him?
What do you remember?
- Couple of pairs of feet. - Faces?
Ian, I promise you I'll talk to you about it, but not here.
It's not safe.
Well, let me tell you how this looks
- from an Office perspective. - Oh, here we go.
You failed another drug test.
You know that's not what this is.
In light of this,
Dwyer's requested a full evaluation.
See if you're fit to return.
He wants you supervised,
followed, monitored.
He could have burned you entirely, but I spoke to him,
bought you some time.
Talk to me, Em.
What's going on?
I can't talk about it now.
We'll fight it.
Pills again, dash of cocaine.
And just last week, I said to myself,
"She's better now.
You don't have to worry."
I'm sorry.
- For what? - For...
not being there.
No, you're not.
And fuck you, by the way.
Do you know what? You don't have to be here anymore.
I thought I needed your help, but I don't.
I want to be here.
Because you feel guilty.
Otherwise, you would have buggered off at the first sight of me.
- I'll go if it makes you feel more comfortable. - Of course.
But I-I would like to stay.
Then stay. Jesus, Dad, what's the matter with you?
We'll get her help.
Good luck trying to convince her.
We'll do it together.
So, who is this friend?
He's originally from my side,
but he now has an identity here.
But you didn't hear that.
Heinrich is here?
Guten tag..
Holy shit.
You're here.
Indeed I am.
Hello.
Good to see you, pal.
Come here.
Local?
Yeah, do you mind giving us a few minutes?
Here, sit.
Brought a little something for you.
Compliments of the other side.
It's good to see you.
I miss this shit.
It's terrible over here.
Nothing like home.
Here's to home.
Cheers.
So, how you doing over here? Okay?
Well, cover is decent.
Um, married a local...
who actually loves me.
You?
I think I'm having a problem with our old friend.
You know anything about this group Pope is working with?
Brought an assassin over here.
Lambert at the embassy's apparently a part of it, too.
Are you sure you want to know about this?
They're fucked up, these people.
Fanatics inside our Office.
And Pope is definitely involved?
Yeah.
He's been helping 'em move illegals a long time now.
He is what he is.
Yeah, yeah, don't...
I don't need the whole fucking speech.
How long ago did he pitch you?
Almost 20 years.
We helped build this network
and you're actually surprised
it's being used for this kind of shit?
Thanks, schatz.
Danke schon.
Five minutes till lunch.
Don't fight him.
Whatever angle you think you have, he's got it covered.
I'm a step ahead of him for the time being, anyway.
Sure about that?
Listen, there's something you should know.
There's a source on the Third Floor over here.
A mole, very high clearance.
They say he's been feeding Pope for years now.
Strategy.
High clearance as in director level?
You don't have a name?
Something's about to happen.
People coming over. Something big.
You go up against Alexander Pope, you'll lose.
- Danke schon. - Danke schon.
Sorry about the mess.
Can I get you anything?
No, thank you.
Make yourself at home.
Just a word on tradecraft.
My ex-husband
wouldn't have brought me home,
wouldn't even have come to the hospital,
and certainly wouldn't have lent me his coat.
Perhaps it'll be simpler if we introduce ourselves.
I'm Emily.
I... I-I don't know what you...
Well, let me guess.
You two were colluding.
He's had you brought over here
so that he can spend more time over there.
I'm... I'm-I'm not... colluding with him.
That's not how it looks, Howard.
He had me brought over here
and kept my locked in an empty apartment.
And what's he doing next?
He's, um...
...he's investigating something.
I-I don't know.
You don't know or you won't tell me?
Believe me, he did not keep me in the loop.
I mean, he told me you were dead.
So, what department do you work for?
Up until just a few days ago, I was in Interface.
Interface?
No, he hasn't worked for them since...
No, I-I know.
He hasn't, but, uh...
I was still there.
Perhaps it's best if we don't talk about everything.
Yes.
Best for everyone.
Why are you looking at me like that?
I'm sorry.
You shouldn't be here.
This isn't usual behavior for him.
It'll attract attention.
Oh, I forgot.
I, uh, invited Anna for dinner.
Is that unusual, too?
Yes.
Hi, Mom.
Dad.
Did you sleep?
What did they say?
They're worried about the situation.
But they're glad you're all right.
They want you to kill me.
We have to find a new crash pad.
It won't be safe for you here.
Three more contracts.
- Nadia. - I can finish the kill list.
You don't know these people like I do.
They don't tolerate mistakes.
Why are you protecting me?
Because I care about you.
You only care about your mission.
Is that who you think I am?
You think I just drop you on the side of the road?
You're not the only one, you know.
When I first crossed over, I watched my other
and her quaint, little life.
She had everything.
She was free and happy.
And I was alone.
Why are you telling me this?
Because it's a choice.
Loneliness.
Let me help you.
You're the only one who knows who I really am
in this whole fucking world,
and I would never let anyone hurt you.
I'm sorry.
No.
Anna.
Dinner is served.
Didn't know you could do anything but barbecue.
Well, I guess, uh...
you learn things living alone.
It's actually really good.
You always mess up a compliment with "Actually."
When did you learn to cook?
A cooking class a while back.
The secret of the chicken is to leave it in the oven
as it cools, and it helps to bring out the flavor.
It's wonderful, actually.
Always was your favorite.
Anna, how's work?
Anything but the subject at hand.
I thought we could wait until dessert.
What's going on here?
Going on?
Are yo...
Are you two getting back together?
- No. - What?
Then stop acting like teenagers.
Okay, let's settle down.
For a second, I thought you gave a shit
about something other than yourself.
- Anna... - Mom overdosed again!
And I'm the only one who seems to care.
Anna, please sit down. Please.
I'm so sick of being your mother.
I'm sick of being the parent to both of you.
That wasn't your fault, you know.
You were no part of that.
I know.
For a moment, it felt like I was, but I know.
Is she like that on your side?
When, uh... when my Emily got pregnant,
we went overboard with the clothes and the room
and the registry.
We wanted everything to be perfect.
I used to lean into her belly
and talk to the baby,
tell her what the world was like.
Seemed like when I did that, she would kick.
But, uh, she miscarried.
I'm so sorry.
We had already picked out the name.
Anna.
Look, I don't... I don't... I don't really know
how it is between you and him.
I mean... I could guess,
knowing him a bit.
But, um...
...however bad it is...
you're both very lucky.
I don't really know you at all, Howard,
but whatever circumstance made you
who you are...
...you're better than him.
I could stay here tonight.
Crash on the couch.
I don't need you to protect me.
I know.
Do you trust this man's intelligence?
He has never been wrong.
So there's a mole,
someone from the other side,
on my floor,
under Aldrich's nose for... years.
I mean, how is that even possible?
Someone got to Emily.
Who's to say they don't know what you're doing, too?
Bottom line is, I'm too exposed.
Until you find out what's what,
I think I need to stay out of it.
And how you gonna do that?
By being him, I guess.
Best I can.
That other Howard, he was with his wife...
...however many years.
He had no idea about her?
No.
I guess loyalty is his biggest flaw.
Mine, too.
Not even a good-bye?
I am clearly writing you a note.
You know, we could help each other.
I mean, the Office are watching me,
but they're not watching you.
There's a lot of stuff going on out there.
We could help him.
Sure.
Yeah, whatever I can do.
That wouldn't be strange for you at all?
Us, together?
I don't know. Would it be strange for you?
Yes.
Yeah, okay.
Okay, now I'm going.
Uh... not taking your pen.
Thank you.
Morning.
I'm going for a walk.
Probably get a cup of tea,
and then, uh, I think I'll just keep walking
and go wherever I want.
I'd like to have his keys.
Thank you.
Next time you talk to him,
tell him I love my new digs.
*Where I lead me I will travel*
*Where I need me I will call me*
*Well, I'm no fool, I'll be ready*
*God knows I will be*
*And in the meantime*
*Make a little money*
*And buy a little mercy*
*Well, met this morning, now she loves me*
*Says she loves me*
*It must be easy, look around you*
*All around you*
*But you see the motion, you're not movin'*
*And you don't know how to hold on*
*You just keep it loose, don't get excited*
*You know it's gonna pass before long*
*Well, one is goin', one is stayin'*