We're beginning our initial
descent into Jackson Hole, Wyoming.
Thank you for ?ying United.
Reckon we'll
be landin' soon.
Phil, honey, you promised.
Not till we got there.
Okay.
This year, we're goin' to a dude
ranch with the whole family.
Mm-hmm.
The family.
What if Dylan
buys his own ticket?
We'll be sleeping
in separate cabins.
What if Dylan and I
share a horse?
Mmm. I hate landing.
We'll get
through this.
Wow. it's so pretty here.
What are you doin'?
I want my ears to pop.
Try putting
a little rouge on 'em.
Nobody gets me.
Wow! isn't this beautiful,
little cowgirl?
You hate her sparkly outfit, don't you?
No, I told you, it's fine.
I just didn't like you
wearing a matching one.
So we haven't told the family yet, but
we've decided to adopt a baby boy.
From America this time. You might
say we're buying domestic.
In private. You might
say that in private.
Our adoption attorney told us
it would be a good idea ...
to make a photo book to
show prospective moms.
Yes. But he thought that Cam's
version was a little too "artsy,"
so we've decided to take a few rugged shots
at the ranch to, you know, balance it out.
I don't think it needs balancing out.
Really?
It's called
production value.
# Hey, hey #
# Hey #
Look. A horse!
Look, Jay! So beautiful!
Your ears haven't
popped yet, huh?
I'm like
the Horse Whisperer!
But something is making
this one skittish!
Whoa.
Look at the mountains.
They're amazing.
I've never been this far from
home before.
Now I've never been
this far.
Now I've never
been this far.
Where's a cliff
when you need one?
Look, kids!
A real-life cowboy!
Come over.
Come see, come see.
Uh-oh.  What's he doing?
Oh, my.
Ooh!
Yeah!
My name is Hank.
Here at the Lost Creek Ranch,
you're gonna ride and you're gonna
rope and you're gonna shoot.
You're gonna see a sky so full of stars,
it'll put your city lights to shame.
And when it's all done,
you might just encounter ...
a piece of yourselves
you never knew was there.
Are there any questions?
Do we book spa treatments
through you or-
I like you, kid.
I'm gonna call you Hollywood.
Th-That wasn't an answer.
And who's
this cactus ?ower?
What?
That's my wife, Gloria.
Well, she's Cactus Flower now,
Old-timer.
These nicknames-
Are they set in stone?
Okeydokey.
You ready, gunslinger?
Heard word of trouble
in these parts.
Pull!
- That oughta fix it, eh, Jay?
- You got a piece of it.
I've been practicing like crazy-
all my cowboy skills.
Shootin', ropin', pancake eatin'.
Why? Because sometimes, I feel like
Jay doesn't respect me as a man.
It's just that when you say
"Phil is my son-in-law,"
it sounds like you're saying,
"Phyllis," comma, "my son-in-law."
That's ridiculous. Okay,
who's your son-in-law?
Phil is.
I'm not asking for a hug. I just want
to get that look of new found respect.
Like-
Oh!
Or-
Or- Mmm. Yeah.
Check it out.
Two birds, one leg.
Pull it!
- Not bad, eh, Old-timer?
- Huh?
See, Slappy only
had three fingers.
- What?
- He only had three fingers!
- Who's next?
- Oh, me, me.
Oh, this is good.
This is good.
Trés macho.
No smile.
Don't smile. Good.
You ready?
Wait, do I say "Pull"?
Sorry, sorry.
Whoa!
Mitchell, why don't you
go find Manny at the spa?
Wouldn't that be more fun?
Yeah.
I realized that if I was gonna raise
a boy, I needed to butch up my life.
You know, I wanted to be able to teach my son
all the things that my dad taught Claire.
Hey, Hollywood.
I don't love that.
You wanna see something?
Oh, my gosh! Is that a firecracker?
Shh!
Now I just need to find
the perfect thing to blow up.
- Is that thing even legal?
- Not here. It's from Germany.
If they had this during the war, right
now we'd all be knee-deep in strudel.
- Watch it!
- What ya doin', eh?
You readin'?
Trying to.
- I'm not so good at it either.
- I'm not surprised.
That was a joke.
I'm Jimmy Scrivano.
You want to see me
do a cannonball?
I'd rather see you get hit by one.
Hah!
Good one, gorgeous.
Hyah!
Jay! Is this
like the lobster?
Do I get to pick one for dinner?
Because this one looks very tender!
Look alive, Old-timer! One of
your calves is gettin' away.
Somethin' wrong with my horse.
She's veering left.
When this happened to my uncle,
it was a stroke.
Oh, there's nothin' wrong with Buttercup.
You just gotta let her know who's boss.
Beautiful form,
Cactus Flower!
Beautiful! You look like
a dadgum conquistadora.
She's deaf,
but I can hear ya.
Why are you
riding that way?
I was afraid that cow
over there might bite me.
Oh, yes, he's gonna come up and bite you because
your leg looks so desirable with those-
Are those canvas?
Okay, Phil, ease that one
back over towards me.
Got it.
Ease him back this way.
Hup-hup! Hey!
- Piece of cake, huh,Jay? - Huh?
- Ease that one over to Bossy.
- Which one's Bossy?
That's my
nickname for your wife.
Hilarious.
Whoa. Whoa.
Go, Mom! Whoo!
Yo, Mom! You rock!
Oh, I wish I had a rock.
Hey. It wouldn't kill you
to be nice to Dylan.
It might.
What- Honey, I don't know why you always stick up for him.
Haley can do so much better.
Because I know what it's like to fall for a
girl whose dad thinks I'm not good enough.
All right. You're right.
I can make more of an effort.
That's the woman I love.
We take a little break over here?
Layin' some pipe?
No, sorry. I was just
talkin' to Bossy. Uh-huh.
Phil!
I'm sorry.
Jay, look!
I got this one!
She's veering left again.
When we get back, I'm gonna see if she
can track a pencil with her eyes.
Okay, Lily, I'm going
to push you one more time.
Now don't kick me, okay?
Lily!
I said don't kick me, okay?
You know, it's your own
fault that's happening.
- Why don't you try standing behind her?
- You are an idiot.
Oh, really? I ain't the
one getting kicked.
Why are you following me? Why are
you fighting me here, gorgeous?
This works.
I really, really don't appreciate
you calling me "gorgeous."
I just want to enjoy time with
my family, so if you don't mind-
Mmm-
Not a problem.
See you around, sunshine.
You kissed a boy!
No, the boy kissed me,
okay, Lily?
Boy kissed me.
# I rode a horse
for the first time today #
# I wasn't surprised
when it went "Neigh" #
- Hey, Dylan.
- Hey. Ms. Dunphy.
I was wondering
if we could have a little chat.
Uh- You want me
to go home.
No. No, it's the-
the opposite of that.
- I want you to go home?
- Mmm. Mm-mmm.
No, I, um- I want you to know
how glad I am that you're here.
Really?
'Cause sometimes I just get
this vibe you don't like me.
No. Dylan, no.
I'm sorry.
L- I like you.
I- I like you a lot. I just-
it's complicated, because ...
Haley's my daughter.
Whoa. Whoa, whoa.
You are totally a hot mom,
but I can't do this.
Oh, my God! Okay.
There's- No, no.
I merely meant that I'm sorry
if I made you feel unwelcome.
- Phew! That would've been awkward.
- So awkward!
You know, but for the
record, Ms. Dunphy-
Yes?
If Haley wasn't
my girlfriend,
and Mr. Dunphy was
out of the picture,
I would be honored
to share your bed ...
and raise Luke, Alex
and Haley as my own.
Okay.
Good talk.
# She'll be runnin'
down the mountain #
# She'll be runnin' down the
mountain when she come g;
The song ended
two minutes ago!
Well, I tell you what.
She could play Evita.
Really? You notice
the crickets left?
Anyone want more water?
Oh, Dad, I'll take one.
Heads up.
Oh, my gosh.
It was- It was dark. I couldn't see it.
Thank you.
So, did you set off
the firecracker yet?
When I do,
you won't have to ask.
First, all the
electronics will go out.
Then comes
the heat flash.
Afterwards, the living
will envy the dead.
And yet I'm the one
on the no-fly list.
Know what? Maybe next time I'll just
catch it and then hand it to you.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, let's do that. You do
everything, and I'll do nothing.
Something on your mind? This isn't
the right place to talk about it.
Okay.
L- I'm just-
I'm not sure if we should
have another baby.
What? Are you serious?
I think that we might be rushing into this.
Rushing into it?
We've been working on-
Everybody.
It's me, Dylan.
I just wanted to thank you all
for bringing me on this trip ...
and making me feel
like one of the family.
- Especially Bossy.
- Aww.
So, I can't think
of a better time ...
to ask something of the
woman that I love.
Okay.
No, no.
Haley Gwendolyn Dunphy, will you do me
the honors of being my lawfully wedded-
No. No, no, no, no! No proposals!
Not now. Not gonna happen.
- She's a child, so-
- Mom!
- You're still in high school!
- I meant after she graduates.
Not then, not now,
not ever.
Seriously, what are you two
gonna live off of?
The royalties from the horsey song?
Put it back in your pocket.
Would you stop it!
No, I won't. I won't.
No, it's okay.
I guess I'll just turn in.
Just so you know, there's a fan in my
cabin that sounds like someone crying.
Oh, God. Dylan, wait!
I hate you!
Oh, come on! Haley, get back here.
Phil? Anything?
I think you said it all, Claire.
You want me to rope her?
I can, you know.
For what it's worth, my second
wife was in high school.
Let's do it again.
One, two, three.
Two, three.
Gone.
it's gone!
It's over there!
it's not back there.
We counted to three!
Yes.
- Hey.
- Where have you been?
I slept on the couch
in the lodge.
- I know you didn't want to have a big fight last night.
- Well, I'm ready now.
Cam, I'm sorry.
Look, what if I can't do
the father-son stuff?
The hunting, the- the sports,
The Three Stooges.
You know what happens in real life when
someone gets hit in the head with a ladder?
They go to the hospital and they get an M.R.I.
Never see that scene.
I think you're
overthinking this.
You know, I love sports. I love the Stooges.
We've got this covered.
No. No, you- you've
got it covered.
I'm just stuck on the sidelines,
pretending to understand the rules and-
You know, my dad was a rough and tumble guy,
and I just- I could never relate to him.
I don't know. I just don't think I could
handle disappointing two generations.
I think you're more masculine than
you give yourself credit for.
Oh, God!
Who puts a birdhouse
next to a porch?
Claire, I know that you're worried that
Dylan is gonna break Haley's heart,
but I see in his eyes that he's
gonna stick with her forever.
No matter what, he's always
going to be with her.
- On your deathbed.
- Okay. All right.
I can't take this anymore.
I'm gonna go find her.
No. You push too hard, you
chase her right into his arms.
You'll end up with a boob for a son-in-law.
Believe me, you don't want that.
- What's that supposed to mean?
- What?
Hey, have you guys
seen Dylan?
No. No, why?
I'm not talking to you.
He said he was going out for a walk last
night, and no one's seen him since.
Sweetheart,
I'm sure he's fine.
Maybe after last night,
he just went home.
Doubt it. He left his luggage.
We have to do something.
If he doesn't eat five times
a day, he gets spacey.
What would that even look like?
We'll find him.
Hank?
We got a situation here!
What seems
to be the trouble?
We need to talk.
What?
You stole my first kiss!
What are you talkin' about?
I had it all planned out.
it was supposed to be special.
Someone with a high G.P.A. and a
bright future, not a Mario Brother.
Fine! You know what?
I don't even want your kiss.
Here, you can
have it back.
There.
Now we're even.
Keep it! I don't- I
don't want it anymore.
What am I doing?
Okay, people.
Looks like we have a walker.
Right now he is facing treacherous
terrain, sudden drops,
mountain lions, hungry bears-
oh, and wolverines.
That is, if the hypothermia
didn't already get him.
Why did we come here again?
So, our best bet
is to split up.
You two are gonna take
to the north hiking trail.
Can I go with my dad instead?
Negative.
I need Buffalo Phil and Old-timer
to check the Snake River.
Buffalo Phil.
Worth the wait.
Me and Cactus Flower will
ride on up to Destiny Ridge.
Maybe I should
ride up there with her.
Negatory. That trail is
for advanced riders only.
- We don't need another dead body.
- "Another"?
Let's go!
Move 'em out.
Phil, help me saddle up
my horse, will you?
Well, look who's suddenly needed
by his father-in-law.
Phyllis.
Phil ... is.
Hey, Uncle Mitch.
What ya doin'?
Oh, hey.
Just- Just thinkin'.
You know, I've been meaning to tell
you, you're a super-fun uncle.
And I'm saying this
as a boy.
Uncle Cameron sent you over here, didn't he?
What? That's hilarious!
No, I love how you and me
can joke like this.
Okay.
Luke, look. I don't know
how much Cam told you,
but I don't think this is a problem
that you can help me with.
Okay, good.
Got my own problem.
Wh- What's that?
Can you keep a secret?
I kept a pretty big one
for 22 years, so-
I've got this new firecracker, and
I can't decide what to blow up.
Oh, Luke, that's dangerous. I know!
That's what's fun about it.
I don't get boys.
What is so great
about destroying things?
It turns stuff into
flying chunks of stuff.
Okay. No. No.
Give it to me.
Fine.
I take it back.
You're not that fun.
All right.
Hey, look, um-
We'll do it together,
all right?
You just made the best
decision of your life.
Okay.
Damn it, Buttercup!
What the hell's wrong
with this horse?
Jay.
Wow.
I want to talk to you about that
son-in-law crack you made at breakfast.
Oh, I didn't mean anything by that!
I think you did.
I get that I wasn't your first choice to
marry Claire, but it's been 18 years,
and there hasn't been a day when I wasn't
a loyal husband to your daughter ...
and a great dad
to your grandkids.
So if we've still got a problem,
now it's your problem.
Phil, wait up.
Can I ask you something, man to man?
Okay.
You notice anything funny
about that Hank character and-
Gloria? Yeah, he's hitting on her.
Why?
I knew it.
Where are you going?
Destiny Ridge.
Buttercup, hyah!
Seriously?
Okay. Okay, it's clear.
After this, we're gonna
have some angry birds.
Yeah. It's gonna
be Bye Bye Birdie.
It's a big musical
from the '60s.
No, forget it.
What you said.
Okay.
Okay. Go!
Cool!
- That's it?
- I'm sorry, buddy.
I brought that thing
all the way from-
Whoa!
Cam!
I did a boy thing!
I blew up the birdhouse!
You should've seen it.
It was so awesome!
That's great!
Yeah.
I think I can do this.
I mean, maybe not everything, and maybe not
right away, and not The Three Stooges.
No.
But ... I do.
I want a son.
I'm sorry I panicked.
Oh, that's great.
Now maybe we can go back
to taking pictures for the book.
Yes! Pictures of me
blowing up stuff!
Okay. I see
we've overcorrected.
I know you think I'm the mean mom who
wouldn't let you marry your boyfriend,
but someday you're gonna realize
I- I did what had to be done.
No, you didn't.
I was never gonna marry Dylan.
I told him no.
You did? Thank God. But it was
my proposal to turn down.
You know, you keep telling me to act like an
adult, but then you don't even give me a chance.
Well, I-
You sort of got me there.
But, sweetheart, I don't
expect you to understand this.
I certainly didn't
when I was your age.
I look at you as my baby,
and I always will.
It's just what moms do.
I'm not a baby anymore, okay?
And I am never gonna
see Dylan again!
Dylan! Dylan!
What?
Where are you?
Wyoming!
- You're okay!
- I had the craziest night.
When you rejected me,
I felt lost and scared.
And then
I went out on a walk,
and I felt a whole different
kind of lost and scared.
Then I fell asleep
in the stable,
and when I woke up, I met this woman
named Jake, who's strong like a man.
Then we had this long talk,
and he- she hired me.
Uh, wha- What do you mean,
she hired you?
I work here now.
So you're staying?
Yeah.
What about us?
It could never work.
We're from
two different worlds.
You're a high school student,
and I'm a ranch hand.
I'm just-
I'm so glad you're okay.
I really am. I am.
Thanks.
But we're not supposed to
fraternize with the guests.
Right.
Dylan!
You got a voice like a
meadowlark, don't ya?
Dylan!
I sure am worried
about that kid.
Dylan-
He ain't down there.
Oh, come on now.
You come up here
for the cowboy experience.
You're lookin' at him.
Do I look like the kind of woman
that would cheat on her husband?
- Yes.
- Really?
Hey! Think you better move
away from that woman.
Only we touch our women
when they don't want us to.
Easy. Easy there, friend-o.
I wasn't hittin' on this filly.
This is all part
of the package.
If I didn't
play the bad guy,
he wouldn't get to ride up
and be the big hero.
He doesn't need you to make him a hero.
He's a hero every day!
Why don't you
do us all a favor?
Get back on your horse, ride
down to the lodge and tell 'em-
Can you keep him still? I'm
trying to make a point. I am.
Okay, okay, I'm gone.
Ma'am.
Wait.
Wait! There's something
I want to say to you.
I will only be checking "somewhat
satisfied" on our comment card.
Oh, geez.
I mean, he was great
with the kids.
I looked it up.
The distance between our houses
is 2,443 miles.
Yeah, but on some maps
it's, like, this big.
God, you're stupid.
All in all,
it was a great vacation.
We may have lost a man,
but out there on the range,
under that great big sky,
we found a part of ourselves
we never knew was there.
Just like the horny cowboy
said we would.
No.
Oh, fine.
English - US - PSDH