. few months[??] ago . started[??] ....... ..... letters[??]
... wrote[??] ... ... letters?
"If .'. .. .. harmed,
"I .... ... .. reach[v.到达，伸手，够到] ... .. ... other[adj.其他的，别的] Howard[??] "
... .. ..... together[adv.共同，一起，同时] .... here?
... .. happy?
. woman[n.妇女，女人] .... ... world[n.世界，...界，世间] ... arrested[??] .. assassin[??]
- .... .... ... Baldwin[??] - ...'. .... illegally,
... . .... .. .... ... ... sent[??] ...
- ... .. concern[v.涉及，关心] - Lambert, ... ambassador[n.大使]
..... .. might[v.或许，可以] .. working[??] .... ..... people[n.人们，人民，人员]
Aldrich, ....'.. kill[v.杀死，杀害] .. all!
Waffe[??] fallen[??] lass!
Leave[v.出发，离开] ....
... didn't[??] .... .... anything, ... you?
.... side[n.边，面，侧面，一方] .. compromised[??]
.'. ... ...... ..'. .... department,
... .'. sure[adj.有把握的，一定的] .. hell[n.地狱，苦境] ... ...... ..'. ...
- ..'.. fucked[??] - ... .. .. send[v.派遣，送，寄出，请] .... ... .... .. .. place[n.地方，位置]
..'.. after[prep.在...后] ... same[adj.同样的] people[n.人们，人民，人员]
.... ..... .. .... .. ...
.... might[v.或许，可以] ... ... same[adj.同样的] .... ...
Oh, .. God
Danke[??]
Gute[??] Nacht[??]
. ... .. work[n.劳动，工作，作品] every[adj.每个，所有的] morning[n.早晨，上午] .. 8:30
.'. ..... late[adj.迟到的，晚的]
Howard[??]
Early, actually,
.. . guess[v.] . ... .. work[n.劳动，工作，作品] .. 8:20-something
Howard[??]
.... ... ... ..... .. there? Packing? ... ... packing?
- ... .... .. might[v.或许，可以] .. . week[n.星期，周，工作周] - ...'.. ..... .. living[adj.活着的]
.. .. life[n.生活，生命，一生] ... don't[??] ....
Forget[v.忘记，疏忽，没想到] ..
Um, after[prep.在...后] work,
I, uh, . .... grab[v.抓住，攫取] . quick[adj.快的，灵敏的] dinner,
... . ... .. ... hospital[n.医院] between[prep.在两者之间] 7:00 ... 7:30
. read[v.读，阅读，朗诵] .. her, ... ... .... ....
Anything[pron.无论什么] else?
Uh, .... mornings[??]
I-I stop[v.停止，终止] ... coffee[n.咖啡] down[adv.向下，下降] .. ... cafe[n.咖啡馆]
Uh, .. Uh, .. play[v.玩，扮演，演奏] ... board[n.木板，伙食，董事会] game[n.游戏，比赛，猎物] ..
.. Tuesdays[??] ... Thursdays, . meet[v.遇到，会见，迎接] . friend[n.朋友]
... name[n.姓名，名称] .. Andrei, and, uh, .. play[v.玩，扮演，演奏] ..
Jesus[n.耶稣]
... know, .... ... ..'. .. great[adj.大的，伟大的]
.. meet[v.遇到，会见，迎接] yourself[pron.你(们)自己]
Bullshit[??]
Kind[n.种类] .. .... losing[??] .... virginity, ... know?
Wait[v.等候，伺候] .... whole[adj.全部的] life[n.生活，生命，一生] ... it,
... .... 20 seconds[??] later, ...'.. disappointed[adj.失望的，扫兴的]
.... ... ... doing?
.. ..... six hours,
.. .... .. become[v.变成] each[adj.] other[adj.其他的，别的]
.... though, apparently, . ... pretty[adj.精致的，漂亮的] .... ..
whatever[pron.无论什么] ... fuck[??蛋，辱?] . want, .. long[adj.长的] .. ..'. ... too exciting[adj.令人激动的]
.. .... remotely[??] interesting[adj.有趣的]
.. .. ...... .... .. ... .. .... each[adj.] other,
...'. play[v.玩，扮演，演奏] cards[??]
So, ...'. ... meet[v.遇到，会见，迎接] .... Andrei?
Uh, .. met .. ... hospital[n.医院]
... sister[n.姊，妹] ... admitted[??] ... same[adj.同样的] day .. Emily[??]
...'. diabetic[??]
Any, uh extracurriculars?
... mean[v.打算，意指]
Jesus, Howard[??] ... ..... any other[adj.其他的，别的] women[??] .. .... life?
.'. married[adj.已婚的]
Did-did ...
.... ... ... ..... alive,
... ... .. .... kind[n.种类] .. thing?
So, ... .. ... .... straight[adj.直的]
.... only[adj.唯一的] friend[n.朋友] .. .... big old city[n.城市] .. .... ...
... didn't[??] .... .... until[prep.] six weeks[??] ago?
Until[prep.] six weeks[??] ago, . ... ...
.... about, uh
.... ..... .... routines?
Don't[??] worry[v.] ..... ..
. work[n.劳动，工作，作品] . desk[n.课桌，写字台] job
... .... absolutely[adv.绝对，完全] .. social[adj.社会的，社会性的] life[n.生活，生命，一生]
..'.. spent[??] ... last[adj.最后的] hour[n.小时，点钟] ..... .... .. stuff,
... ... .. I-I don't[??] .... what,
... .... answer[n.答案] is, "Don't worry[v.] ..... it"?
Yeah[??] . ... . ...
... name[n.姓名，名称] .. Raash[??] ..'.. .... care[n.注意，小心] .. ...
... .. realize[v.认识到，实现，执行] ..'.. ... same[adj.同样的] person, right? Essentially[adj.本质上，实质上]
. mean, ... same[adj.同样的] flesh[n.肌肉，骨肉，果肉] ... blood, ... same[adj.同样的] DNA
Yeah[??] ....... me, . ..
.... ... .. ... .... compelled[??] .. treat[v.对待，医治，论述] .. .. badly?
..'. .... bet
... flopped[??] top pair, ... ...'.. folding?
.... ... . .... bluff[??]
.. .. . favor, .... you?
Play[v.玩，扮演，演奏] ... hand[n.手，人手，指针] .... ... actually[adv.实际上，居然] .... ... .. win
Howard, play[v.玩，扮演，演奏] ... fucking[??] hand[n.手，人手，指针]
... .. finished?
.. ... .... notice[v.留意] ... ....
Fresh[adj.新鲜的，崭新的] clothes[n.衣服(总称)]
Weapon?
... .... .. their[adj.他们的，它们的] custody[n.保管，监护] ... hours[??]
.... ... .... ask you?
.'. sorry[adj.难过的，遗憾的]
..... .... happened[??] .. .... other[adj.其他的，别的]
...'. dead[adj.死的]
... . .... .... nothing[n.没有东西]
.'.. .... .. .... ..... next[adv.下一次，然后] steps[??] ... .... rest[v.休息]
Howard, ..'. ....
Well, well, well[n.井]
...'.. saving[??] ... .... stuff, huh?
....'. ... ... .. .. ...
..'. ... .... ... wakes[??] ..
.... ... week[n.星期，周，工作周]
...'.. ..... ... ..... .....
....'.. ..... ... through[prep.通过，借助] ..
... .. ... keep[v.保持，保留，防止] .... mouth[n.口，嘴巴，河口] shut[v.关闭，合拢]
...'.. read[v.读，阅读，朗诵] .. ... every[adj.每个，所有的] day
. ....
Keep[v.保持，保留，防止] ... safe[adj.安全的，无风险的]
.... ..... people[n.人们，人民，人员]
Howard[??]
.'.. .... him, Cyrus, .... ....
..... ...
.. ... .... ... paperwork?
Yeah[??]
... ..... .... don't[??] .. that, .. ... way
What?
Shake[v.摇动，发抖，握手] hands[??] Berlin, .. ... other[adj.其他的，别的] side, ....
...'.. ... ..'. . germ[n.萌芽，起源，细菌] .....
.... .. ....
Howard, .. ... ... caught,
.....'. .. ... .. protect[v.保护，警戒] ... .... .....
... understand? ...'.. .. .... own
Yeah[??]
. .... .. deny[v.否认，拒绝] any part[n.部分，零件，角色] .. ....
Okay[??] ..... ...
Danke[??]
Arms[n.武器] ..
Yours?
Oh, shit, . forgot[??]
Oh, .... on, ..'. .... . pack[v.包装，挤满] .. bloody[adj.流血的，残忍的] smokes[??]
Oh, ... God's[??] sake, .. ... .... . mistake[n.错误，误解]
.... on, really?
Sir?
Purpose[n.目的，用途，意图] .. visit?
Uh, the, uh, embassy[n.使馆] pouch[??]
Welcome[adj.受欢迎的] home[n.家，故乡]
.'. Raash[??]
..... ...
Hey! Hey! ....
.... on, .... ... ... ?
. ...... sparse[a.稀少的，贫乏的]
. .... . few contacts[??] left[adj.左的] .. ... embassy[n.使馆]
..'.. ... .... escorts[??] .. Lambert[??]
.. .. ... any connections[??] .. Baldwin, .. men .... .... ...
.. ... ever[adv.曾经，总是，究竟] .... doubts[??] ..... ..... men?
.'. .... wondering[??] ... ..'.. always[adv.总是，始终] ....
... step[n.脚步，台阶，步骤] behind[prep.在...后面] ....
'Cause[??] ..'.. .... meticulous, right?
.. ... vetting[??] . mean, .....'. ..
.....'. .. chance[n.机会，可能性] .. any point[n.尖，点，分] .. compromise[n.] here, .. there?
... unless[prep.除非] ... count[v.计算，数，认为] Howard[??] Silk[n.丝，绸]
... promoted[??] ...
Well, .... ... ... deal[v.处理，交易]
... other's[??] ....
- ... .... deals? - Because, candidly[??] speaking,
.... man's[??] .... . lot .... useful[adj.有用的，有益的] than[conj.比，除...外] .... lot lately,
... .'. .... .. stay[v.停留，暂住，保持] .. ... .... side[n.边，面，侧面，一方]
... ..... anything[pron.无论什么] else?
Ah, finally, .... send[v.派遣，送，寄出，请] help[v.]
....... . ... ..... .. .. Strategy[n.战略，策略，计谋]
Yes, .... .. .. Strategy[n.战略，策略，计谋] payroll[??]
... .... . degree[n.程度，度，学位] .. accounting, yeah?
..
.... desk[n.课桌，写字台]
.... ..... .... . .. .. . joke,
.. ... .... play[v.玩，扮演，演奏] . joke[n.笑话] .. ..
.... .. file[n.档案，纵列，锉刀] every[adj.每个，所有的] .... card, mark[n.痕迹，符号，标记] .. .... code, send[v.派遣，送，寄出，请] .. ....
... .... too long, . .... .... someone[pron.有人，某人] .. replace[v.归还原处，代替] ...
Questions?
Uh, ..... ... ... going?
Personal[adj.私人的，个人的] day
.... .. wrong[adj.错误的，有毛病的] .... you?
.... .. ... ... idea, . assume?
Groceries[??]
So, .... .. it?
.... ... ... me, locked[??] .. .... apartment[n.套房，公寓] ... . week?
God, .'. such[adj.这样的，如此的] .. idiot[n.傻子，白痴]
Open[adj.开的] ... door[n.门，(一户)人家]
. .... ... Raash[??] .. .. .....
. .... ...'.. .. .....
Dad!
.... phone's[??] .... off ... day
Mom's[??] .. ... hospital, ..'.. ... .. go, .... ..
- Mom? - Yes
.... mom?
Obviously[adv.明显地，显然] .... ... .... jacket[n.短外套，茄克衫]
.... .. .... ..
Anna?
What?
What, uh .... happened[??] .. .... mother?
.. ... another[pron.] overdose[n.(药物)过度剂量]
Yeah[??] Neighbors[??] ..... ... .. ... floor[n.地板，(楼)层]
Barely[adv.赤裸裸地] ... . pulse[n.脉搏]
...'. probably[adv.或许，大概] .... ..... ... night[n.夜，黑夜]
...'.. actually[adv.实际上，居然] surprised?
I-I'm . lot .. ...... ..... ...
Yeah, well, don't[??] worry[v.] ... don't[??] .... .. .. anything[pron.无论什么]
.'.. deal[v.处理，交易] .... ... doctors[??] .... .. ... .....
.....
Yeah[??] O-Of course[n.过程，路线，课程]
. ... ...
... escorts[??] ...
... .... reason, .... ..... .'. using[??] ..... appointments[??]
... clandestine[a.秘密的，暗中从事的] meetings[??]
So, ..... .. she?
... ..... .. keep[v.保持，保留，防止] working[??]
.... ... .... .... nothing[n.没有东西]
.... ... ... .... .... nothing[n.没有东西]
.... ... heard[??] anything[pron.无论什么] .... home?
Towel, please[v.使高兴，喜欢，请]
.... friends[??] ... ... happy[adj.高兴的，幸运的]
.... ... ...... .... .... developing[adj.发展中的]
.... .... .. bring[v.拿来，带来] .... ... guests[??] earlier[??] than[conj.比，除...外] expected[??]
... hasn't[??] removed[??] ... targets[??] yet
... .. .... note,
.... also[adv.也] raised[??] questions[??]
..... .... assassin[??] friend[n.朋友]
First[adj.第一的] .... push[v.推，推动] .. ... .. .. airplane[n.飞机]
... .... .... .... away[adv.去，远离，在远处] .. chute[??]
.... .... ... removed[??]
... trusts[??] ..
....'. ....... .. lightly, .... .... . hear[v.听见，听取，听说]
Perhaps[adv.也许，多半] ..'. ....
... actually[adv.实际上，居然] use .... situation[n.形势，局面] .. .... advantage[n.优点，优势]
Clare[??]
. ...'. imagine[v.想象，猜想] ... pressure[n.压力，繁忙，紧迫] ...'.. under[prep.在...下面]
... weight[n.重量，重担，重物] .. ..... expectations[??]
... after[prep.在...后] ... ... work[n.劳动，工作，作品] .... .... ... .. place[n.地方，位置] ... here,
..... ... ...... risk[n.] .... mission[n.使团，使命，天职]
.... ..'.. .. close[down] .. ... big day?
.'.. .... care[n.注意，小心] .. ..
... always[adv.总是，始终] ..
... ... ... feeling?
Thirsty[adj.渴的，渴望的]
Jesus, Em
.... happened?
..... .... reason[n.原因，理由] ...'.. here, Howard?
.'.
Well, ..... ... ... ......
- .'.. ... .. - ..... ...
... .... dicks[??] away, please?
"Light . candle[n.蜡烛] .. St Christopher's[??] "
.... ... fuck[??蛋，辱?] .... .... .... mean?
... .... .. .... .... .'. ........ ..... now, ... prick?
.'. ........ .... .. .. ...
Stay[v.停留，暂住，保持] ... fuck[??蛋，辱?] away[adv.去，远离，在远处] .... ...
Really? .... walk[v.步行，走] ... .. ... middle[n.当中] .. ... day?
... .... .. .. any .... conspicuous?
.... ... .... idea[n.思想，主意，打算] .. . promotion?
- Payroll? - Well, .'. sorry[adj.难过的，遗憾的]
.. ... ... .... . ..... .. .... ten seconds'[??] notice[v.留意]
Okay, .... .. ... .... ..... this, uh, Lambert?
Nothing[n.没有东西]
. don't[??] know, .. ... men .. ... ... ... time,
... ..'. . high-ranking diplomat, ..
- Really? - What?
...'.. married[adj.已婚的] .. . director's[??] daughter, right?
Yeah[??] So?
.... ... hell's[??] .. marriage[n.婚姻，婚礼] ... .. ?
.'.. .... ... .... . ... .. .. own career[n.职业，生涯] trajectory[n.(抛射物)弹道轨道]
long[adj.长的] before[prep.在...前面] . met Roland[??] Fancher's[??] daughter[n.女儿]
- Okay[??] - Yeah, ... . resent[v.不满于，愤恨] ... implication[n.暗示，含义]
.'. fucking[??] .... .. .. job,
... .... .. ..... .. .. work, Howard[??] Silk,
nothing[n.没有东西] .... past[adj.过去的] ..
.. . guess[v.] ... .... ... ..... other[adj.其他的，别的] Howard's[??] wife, then, huh?
... ... .. agent[n.代理人，试剂]
Housekeeping? Under[prep.在...下面] Aldrich[??]
... .. ... .... that?
'Cause[??] ... ... .. contact[n.]
... reached[??] ... .. .. months[??] ago,
.... ...... .. .... floor[n.地板，(楼)层] .... compromised,
... couldn't[??] trust[n.v.委托，信任，信托] anybody,
... .... ... ... . ...... accident[n.事故，意外之事]
... ... .... ... ..... that, right?
'Cause[??] nothing[n.没有东西] .... past[adj.过去的] ...
... .... .. ... fucking[??] Office[n.办公室，事务所]
.'. meeting[n.会议，集会] . friend[n.朋友] .... afternoon[n.下午]
Who?
.. old friend[n.朋友] Don't[??] worry[v.] ..... ..
... right, ..'.. ..... .... .. establish[v.建立，设立，确立]
. few fucking[??] ground[n.地面，场，根据] rules[??] ....
Both[pron.] .. ... lives[??] ... .. ... line[n.行，线条，界线]
....... .. .... arrangement,
.. ... ...'. wander[v.徘徊，离题，迷失] around[adv.在周围，大约] .. world[n.世界，...界，世间]
.... ..'. .... fucking[??] playground[n.运动场，操场]
..'.. .. lockstep[??] .... ... ..
.. ... .. .... friend, ... .... ... .. meeting[n.会议，集会] him?
.... .. ... remember?
- Couple[n.一对，几个，夫妇] .. pairs[??] .. feet[??] - Faces?
Ian, . promise[v.允诺，预示] ... .'.. .... .. ... ..... it, ... ... ....
..'. ... safe[adj.安全的，无风险的]
Well, ... .. .... ... ... .... .....
- .... .. Office[n.办公室，事务所] perspective[n.展望，观点，透视] - Oh, .... .. ..
... failed[??] another[pron.] drug[n.药物，麻醉剂] test[v.]
... .... ....'. ... .... .... ..
.. light[n.光，灯] .. this,
Dwyer's[??] requested[??] . full[adj.满的，完全的] evaluation[n.估价，评价]
... .. ...'.. fit .. return[v.回归，归还]
.. ..... ... supervised,
followed, monitored[??]
.. ..... .... burned[??] ... entirely, ... . spoke[n.(车轮上)幅条，阻碍物] .. him,
bought[??] ... .... ....
.... .. me, Em
....'. ..... on?
. ...'. .... ..... .. ...
..'.. fight[v.打仗，战斗，作斗争] ..
Pills[??] again, dash[v.猛冲] .. cocaine[??]
... .... last[adj.最后的] week, . .... .. myself,
"She's ...... ...
... don't[??] .... .. worry[v.] "
.'. sorry[adj.难过的，遗憾的]
- ... what? - ...
... ..... .....
No, ...'.. ...
... fuck[??蛋，辱?] you, .. ... way
.. ... .... what? ... don't[??] .... .. .. .... anymore[??]
. ....... . ...... .... help, ... . don't[??]
. .... .. .. ....
....... ... .... guilty[adj.有罪的，内疚的]
Otherwise, ... ..... .... buggered[??] off .. ... first[adj.第一的] sight[n.视力，情景] .. ..
- .'.. .. .. .. ..... ... .... .... comfortable[adj.舒适的，自在的] - .. course[n.过程，路线，课程]
... I-I ..... .... .. stay[v.停留，暂住，保持]
.... stay[v.停留，暂住，保持] Jesus, Dad, ....'. ... matter[n.事情，物资，毛病] .... you?
..'.. ... ... help[v.]
.... luck[n.运气，幸运] ...... .. convince[v.使...确信，信服] ...
..'.. .. .. together[adv.共同，一起，同时]
So, ... .. .... friend?
..'. originally[adv.原来，当初] .... .. side,
... .. ... ... .. identity[n.认同，同一性] ....
... ... didn't[??] hear[v.听见，听取，听说] ....
Heinrich[??] .. here?
Guten[??] tag
Holy[adj.神圣的，圣洁的] shit[??]
...'.. ....
Indeed[adv.的确，实际上] . ..
Hello[int.喂，你好]
.... .. ... you, pal
.... ....
Local?
Yeah, .. ... mind[n.头脑，智力] ...... .. . few minutes?
Here, sit
Brought[??] . ...... ......... ... ...
Compliments[??] .. ... other[adj.其他的，别的] side[n.边，面，侧面，一方]
..'. .... .. ... ...
. miss[v.未击中] .... shit[??]
..'. terrible[adj.可怕的，极度的] .... ....
Nothing[n.没有东西] .... home[n.家，故乡]
....'. .. home[n.家，故乡]
Cheers[??]
So, ... ... ..... .... here? Okay?
Well, cover[v.盖，掩盖] .. decent[adj.体面的，象样的]
Um, married[adj.已婚的] . local[adj.地方的，当地的]
... actually[adv.实际上，居然] ..... ..
You?
. ..... .'. ...... . problem[n.课题，难题，问题] .... ... old friend[n.朋友]
... .... anything[pron.无论什么] ..... .... group[n.群，组，团体] Pope[n.教皇] .. working[??] with?
Brought[??] .. assassin[??] .... ....
Lambert[??] .. ... embassy's[??] apparently[adj.显然，似乎] . part[n.部分，零件，角色] .. it, too
... ... sure[adj.有把握的，一定的] ... .... .. .... ..... this?
....'.. fucked[??] up, ..... people[n.人们，人民，人员]
Fanatics[??] inside[n.里面] ... Office[n.办公室，事务所]
... Pope[n.教皇] .. definitely[adv.明确地，肯定地] involved?
Yeah[??]
..'. .... helping[n.一份或一客食物] 'em move[v.移动，推动，搬家] illegals[??] . long[adj.长的] .... ...
.. .. .... .. ..
Yeah, yeah, don't[??]
. don't[??] .... ... whole[adj.全部的] fucking[??] speech[n.演说，语言能力]
... long[adj.长的] ago ... .. pitch[v.搭帐篷，投掷] you?
Almost[adv.几乎，差不多] 20 years[??]
.. helped[??] build[v.建造，建设] .... network[n.网络，网状组织]
... ...'.. actually[adv.实际上，居然] surprised[??]
..'. ..... used[??] ... .... kind[n.种类] .. shit?
Thanks, schatz[??]
Danke[??] schon[??]
Five[num.五] minutes[??] till[prep.直到] lunch[n.午饭，便餐]
Don't[??] fight[v.打仗，战斗，作斗争] ...
Whatever[pron.无论什么] angle[n.角，角度] ... ..... ... have, ..'. ... .. covered[??]
.'. . step[n.脚步，台阶，步骤] ahead[adv.在...前] .. ... ... ... .... being, anyway[adv.不管怎样]
Sure[adj.有把握的，一定的] ..... that?
Listen, .....'. ......... ... ...... ....
.....'. . source[n.来源，出处，源泉] .. ... Third[num.第三，三分之一] Floor[n.地板，(楼)层] .... ....
. mole, very[adv.很，非常] high[adj.高的，高度的] clearance[n.结关]
.... ... ..'. .... feeding[??] Pope[n.教皇] ... years[??] ...
Strategy[n.战略，策略，计谋]
High[adj.高的，高度的] clearance[n.结关] .. .. director[n.指导者，导演，领导] level?
... don't[??] .... . name?
.........'. ..... .. happen[v.发生，碰巧，出事]
People[n.人们，人民，人员] ...... .... ......... big
... .. .. against[prep.反对，对着] Alexander[??] Pope, ...'.. lose[v.失去，丢失，输]
- Danke[??] schon[??] - Danke[??] schon[??]
Sorry[adj.难过的，遗憾的] ..... ... mess[n.肮脏，凌乱]
... . ... ... anything?
No, ..... ...
.... yourself[pron.你(们)自己] .. home[n.家，故乡]
.... . word[n.字，词，诺言，音讯] .. tradecraft[??]
.. ex-husband
wouldn't[??] .... brought[??] .. home,
wouldn't[??] .... .... .... .. ... hospital,
... certainly[adv.一定，当然，行] wouldn't[??] .... lent[??] .. ... coat[n.上衣，涂层]
Perhaps[adv.也许，多半] ..'.. .. simpler[??] .. .. introduce[v.介绍，引进，采用] ourselves[pron.我们自己]
.'. Emily[??]
. I-I don't[??] .... .... ...
Well, ... .. guess[v.]
... ... .... colluding[??]
..'. ... ... brought[??] .... ....
.. .... .. ... spend[v.花费，消耗] .... .... .... .....
.'. I'm-I'm ... colluding[??] .... ...
....'. ... ... .. looks, Howard[??]
.. ... .. brought[??] .... ....
... kept[??] .. locked[??] .. .. empty[adj.空的，空虚的] apartment[n.套房，公寓]
... ....'. .. ..... next?
He's, um
..'. investigating[??] .........
I-I don't[??] ....
... don't[??] .... .. ... won't[??] .... me?
....... me, .. ... ... keep[v.保持，保留，防止] .. .. ... loop[n.环，回路]
. mean, .. .... .. ... .... dead[adj.死的]
So, .... department[n.部，部门，系] .. ... work[n.劳动，工作，作品] for?
.. until[prep.] .... . few days[??] ago, . ... .. Interface[n.交界，接口]
Interface?
No, .. hasn't[??] worked[??] ... .... since[prep.自从]
No, I-I ....
.. hasn't, but, uh
. ... ..... .....
Perhaps[adv.也许，多半] ..'. .... .. .. don't[??] .... ..... everything[pron.事事，一切]
Yes
.... ... everyone[pron.人人，每人]
... ... ... ....... .. .. .... that?
.'. sorry[adj.难过的，遗憾的]
... shouldn't[??] .. ....
.... isn't[??] usual[adj.通常的，习惯性的] behavior[n.行为，举止] ... ...
..'.. attract[v.吸引，引力] attention[n.注意，关心]
Oh, . forgot[??]
I, uh, invited[??] Anna[??] ... dinner[n.正餐，晚餐，宴会]
.. .... unusual, too?
Yes
Hi, Mom
Dad
... ... sleep?
.... ... .... say?
....'.. worried[??] ..... ... situation[n.形势，局面]
... ....'.. glad[adj.快乐的，高兴的] ...'.. ... .....
.... .... ... .. kill[v.杀死，杀害] ..
.. .... .. .... . new crash[v.碰撞] pad
.. won't[??] .. safe[adj.安全的，无风险的] ... ... ....
Three[num.三] .... contracts[??]
- Nadia[??] - . ... finish[v.] ... kill[v.杀死，杀害] list[n.表，名单]
... don't[??] .... ..... people[n.人们，人民，人员] .... . ..
.... don't[??] tolerate[v.容忍，宽容] mistakes[??]
... ... ... protecting[??] me?
....... . care[n.注意，小心] ..... ...
... only[adj.唯一的] care[n.注意，小心] ..... .... mission[n.使团，使命，天职]
.. .... ... ... ..... . am?
... ..... . .... drop[v.落下] ... .. ... side[n.边，面，侧面，一方] .. ... road?
...'.. ... ... only[adj.唯一的] one, ... ....
.... . first[adj.第一的] crossed[??] over, . watched[??] .. other[adj.其他的，别的]
... ... quaint, ...... life[n.生活，生命，一生]
... ... everything[pron.事事，一切]
... ... free[adj.自由的，空闲的] ... happy[adj.高兴的，幸运的]
... . ... alone[adj.单独的，仅仅]
... ... ... ....... .. this?
....... ..'. . choice[n.选择，选中的人或物]
Loneliness[n.孤独，寂寞]
... .. help[v.] ...
...'.. ... only[adj.唯一的] ... ... ..... ... . ...... ..
.. .... whole[adj.全部的] fucking[??] world,
... . ..... ..... ... anyone[pron.无论谁] hurt[v.使受伤，使痛，伤害] ...
.'. sorry[adj.难过的，遗憾的]
..
Anna[??]
Dinner[n.正餐，晚餐，宴会] .. served[??]
Didn't[??] .... ... ..... .. anything[pron.无论什么] ... barbecue[n.烤肉架，烤肉]
Well, . guess, uh
... learn[v.学习，获悉] ...... living[adj.活着的] alone[adj.单独的，仅仅]
..'. actually[adv.实际上，居然] ...... ....
... always[adv.总是，始终] mess[n.肮脏，凌乱] .. . compliment[n.] .... "Actually "
.... ... ... learn[v.学习，获悉] .. cook?
. cooking[??] class[n.阶级，种类，班级] . while[n.一会儿] ....
... secret[adj.秘密的] .. ... chicken[n.鸡，鸡肉] .. .. leave[v.出发，离开] .. .. ... oven[n.烤炉，锅灶]
.. .. cools, ... .. helps[??] .. bring[v.拿来，带来] ... ... flavor[n.滋味，风趣]
..'. wonderful, actually[adv.实际上，居然]
Always[adv.总是，始终] ... .... favorite[n.adj.最喜爱的人或物]
Anna, ...'. work?
Anything[pron.无论什么] ... ... subject[n.题目，学科，主语] .. hand[n.手，人手，指针]
. ....... .. ..... wait[v.等候，伺候] until[prep.] dessert[n.(最后一道)甜食]
....'. ..... .. here?
..... on?
... yo
... ... ... ....... .... together?
- .. - What?
.... stop[v.停止，终止] acting[??] .... teenagers[??]
Okay, ...'. settle[v.解决，安置，支付] down[adv.向下，下降]
... . second, . ....... ... .... . shit[??]
..... ......... other[adj.其他的，别的] than[conj.比，除...外] yourself[pron.你(们)自己]
- Anna[??] - Mom overdosed[??] again!
... .'. ... only[adj.唯一的] ... ... seems[??] .. care[n.注意，小心]
Anna, please[v.使高兴，喜欢，请] sit down[adv.向下，下降] Please[v.使高兴，喜欢，请]
.'. .. sick[adj.有病的，厌恶的] .. ..... .... mother[n.母亲]
.'. sick[adj.有病的，厌恶的] .. ..... ... parent[n.父或母亲，母体] .. both[pron.] .. ...
.... wasn't[??] .... fault, ... ....
... .... .. part[n.部分，零件，角色] .. ....
. ....
... . moment, .. .... .... . was, ... . ....
.. ... .... .... .. .... side?
When, uh .... .. Emily[??] ... pregnant,
.. .... overboard[??] .... ... clothes[n.衣服(总称)] ... ... room[n.房间，室，空间]
... ... registry[??]
.. ...... everything[pron.事事，一切] .. .. perfect[adj.完美的，完备的]
. used[??] .. lean[v.俯身，倚] into[prep.到...里面，..成] ... belly[n.肚子]
... .... .. ... baby,
.... ... .... ... world[n.世界，...界，世间] ... ....
Seemed[??] .... .... . ... that, ... ..... kick[v.]
But, uh, ... miscarried[??]
.'. .. sorry[adj.难过的，遗憾的]
.. ... already[??] picked[??] ... ... name[n.姓名，名称]
Anna[??]
Look, . don't[??] . don't[??] . don't[??] ...... ....
... .. .. between[prep.在两者之间] ... ... ...
. mean[v.打算，意指] . ..... guess,
....... ... . bit
But, um
however[adv.可是，然而] bad .. ..
...'.. both[pron.] very[adv.很，非常] lucky[adj.幸运的]
. don't[??] ...... .... ... .. all, Howard,
... whatever[pron.无论什么] circumstance[n.情况，环境] .... ...
... ... ...
...'.. ...... than[conj.比，除...外] ...
. ..... stay[v.停留，暂住，保持] .... tonight[n.今晚]
Crash[v.碰撞] .. ... couch[n.躺椅]
. don't[??] .... ... .. protect[v.保护，警戒] ..
. ....
.. ... trust[n.v.委托，信任，信托] .... man's[??] intelligence?
.. ... ..... .... wrong[adj.错误的，有毛病的]
.. .....'. . mole,
someone[pron.有人，某人] .... ... other[adj.其他的，别的] side,
.. .. floor,
under[prep.在...下面] Aldrich's[??] nose[n.鼻子] ... years[??]
. mean, ... .. .... .... possible?
Someone[pron.有人，某人] ... .. Emily[??]
...'. .. ... .... don't[??] .... .... ...'.. doing, too?
Bottom[n.底部，末尾] line[n.行，线条，界线] is, .'. too exposed[??]
Until[prep.] ... .... ... ....'. what,
. ..... . .... .. stay[v.停留，暂住，保持] ... .. ..
... ... ... ..... .. that?
.. ..... him, . guess[v.]
.... . ...
.... other[adj.其他的，别的] Howard, .. ... .... ... wife[n.妻子，夫人]
however[adv.可是，然而] many[adj.许多的] years[??]
.. ... .. idea[n.思想，主意，打算] ..... her?
..
. guess[v.] loyalty[n.忠诚，忠贞] .. ... biggest[??] flaw[n.裂缝，瑕疵，缺点]
Mine, too
... .... . good-bye?
. .. clearly[adv.清晰地，无疑地] writing[n.写作] ... . note[n.笔记，注释，便条]
... know, .. ..... help[v.] each[adj.] other[adj.其他的，别的]
. mean, ... Office[n.办公室，事务所] ... watching[??] me,
... ....'.. ... watching[??] ...
.....'. . lot .. stuff[n.材料，东西] ..... .. ... .....
.. ..... help[v.] ...
Sure[adj.有把握的，一定的]
Yeah, whatever[pron.无论什么] . ... ..
.... wouldn't[??] .. strange[adj.奇怪的，陌生的] ... ... .. all?
Us, together?
. don't[??] .... ..... .. .. strange[adj.奇怪的，陌生的] ... you?
Yes
Yeah, okay[??]
Okay, ... .'. .....
Uh ... ...... .... pen
..... ...
Morning[n.早晨，上午]
.'. ..... ... . walk[v.步行，走]
Probably[adv.或许，大概] ... . cup .. tea,
... then, uh, . ..... .'.. .... keep[v.保持，保留，防止] walking[??]
... .. wherever[adv.无论哪里] . ....
.'. .... .. .... ... keys[??]
..... ...
Next[adv.下一次，然后] .... ... .... .. him,
.... ... . .... .. new digs[??]
..... . lead[v.引导，领先，率领] .. . .... travel[v.旅行，传导]
..... . .... .. . .... .... ..
Well, .'. .. fool, .'.. .. ready[adj.准备好的，乐意的]
God ..... . .... ..
... .. ... meantime[adv.同时，在这期间]
.... . ...... money[n.金钱，货币，财富]
... buy . ...... mercy[n.宽大，慈悲，怜悯]
Well, met .... morning, ... ... ..... ..
.... ... ..... ..
.. must[v.必须，准是] .. easy, .... around[adv.在周围，大约] ...
... around[adv.在周围，大约] ...
... ... ... ... motion, ...'.. ... movin'[??]
... ... don't[??] .... ... .. hold[v.握住，容纳] ..
... .... keep[v.保持，保留，防止] .. loose, don't[??] ... excited[adj.兴奋的]
... .... ..'. ..... pass[v.经过，传给] before[prep.在...前面] long[adj.长的]
Well, ... .. goin', ... .. stayin'[??]